Seth Angell

Charlotte, North Carolina

□+1.704.517.3957 | Seth@probit.live | GethAngell | SethAngell



Summary_

Undergraduate research assistant at the University of North Carolina - Wilmington and co-founder & software engineer at Probit Technologies. Proficiencies include Python, Django, HTML/CSS, Java, C#, Android Studio, Databases, and Unity3D. Podcast lover and Apple enthusiast who enjoys bringing a creative flair to the project. Passions involve generating software and hardware solutions to allow users to spend less time tinkering with platforms and more time creating the things they love.

Education

University Of North Carolina At Wilmington

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - SYSTEMS CONCENTRATION

Member of the UNCW Honors College - 3.7 GPA

• Deans List - 2017-2018, Spring 2019

Wilmington, North Carolina

May 2021

Work Experience ___

University Of North Carolina - Wilmington

Undergraduate Researcher

Wilmington, North Carolina

January 2019 - PRESENT

- Working under the guidance of Dr. Toni Pence. Current goals include the research and development of mixed reality interfaces, with a focus on immersive data analytics and forensics.
- Utilizing Unity3D and the windows MRTK for front end development, which we've connected to a backend software stack consisting of MySQL, Java, and the Spring Boot framework. Targeted devices include the HTC Vive, Oculus Quest, as well as the Magic Leap.

The Technology Assistance Center - UNCW

TIER 1 SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Wilmington, North Carolina

Aug 2018 - February 2019

- Research and codify varying IT issues in order to provide on demand phone and in person support to students, faculty, and staff.
- Triage technology issues among varying levels of authority within the company, while ensuring customer satisfaction stays high.
- Handle the inventory of rental machines, and regular cashed out registers during closing procedures.

PROBIT TECHNOLOGIES LP

Charlotte, North Carolina

May 2018 - PRESENT

- CO-FOUNDER & SOFTWARE ENGINEER
- Produced pilot software for fortune 50 company, Mondelez International.
- Generate action plans, host team meetings, and handle client communications, in order to effectively move projects to the next milestone
- Oversee financial activity, advise on future spending, and generate and manage new sales leads, in the pursuit of future company profits.

Audio Video Smart Solutions

Charlotte, North Carolina

May 2018 - July 2018

SMART HOME TECHNICIAN

Extracurricular Activity _____

Probit.Live (Podcast)

Wilmington, North Carolina

Producer & Host

Fall 2017

- Hosted a multimedia podcast highlighting the songs that make up the background of our lives.
- Coordinated guest scheduling, edited audio projects, and produced an 8 episode series of hour long episodes.

Skills_

- Programming languages include: Python, Django, Java, C#, Android Studio, HTML/CSS, MySQL, Apache Tomcat, and Unity3D.
- Proficient in the Adobe Creative Suites, Microsoft Office, and MacOS and Windows environments.